http://www.internethobbies.com/pages/internet-hobbies-online-privacy-agreement

Unimodel
Williams Bros.
BROADWAY LIMITED
B.T.S.
Latest posts
COVID-19 - HOW HAS IT AFFECTED THE HOBBY INDUSTRY AND YOUR ORDER?
Many of our customers have been waiting patiently for their orders to be delivered. Most...
What Is MSRP?
WHAT IS MSRP? MSRP or Manufacturer's Suggested Retail Price is the list price of a manufacturer's products....
LOOK AT THE DIFFERENCE IN RETAIL PRICES BETWEEN THEM AND US
It just amazes us how the big shots in Texas get away with their crazy...
HK MODELS ANNOUNCED A 1/48 B-17G EARLY PRODUCTION KIT
The newest kit from Hong Kong Models of their Boeing B-17 scale is coming...
Tamiya Has Announced Their New 1/48 Scale Lockheed P-38®F/G Lightning Kit
Tamiya has now confirmed their new-tool kit of the Lockheed P-38®F/G Lightning in 1/48th scale...
Wishlist (0)
Newsletter
Sign up to our newsletter for the latest news and special offers.
Subscribe
Popular products
Academy Aircraft 1/48 F4J Diamondbacks USN Fighter Kit
$69.00 $54.99
Academy Military 1/35 PzKpfw V Panther Ausf G Last Production Tank (New Tool) Kit
$52.00 $41.60
HK Models 1/48 B17G Flying Fortress Heavy Bomber (New Tool) Kit
$139.95 $111.96
Hobby Boss Aircraft 1/32 A-26B Invader Kit
$229.99 $183.99
Hobby Boss Military 1/72 German KARL-Geraet 040/041 on Railway Transport Carrier Kit
$48.99 $39.19
ICM Military Models 1/24 SEAL Team Fighter #1 (New Tool) Kit
$24.99 $19.99
Italeri Military 1/35 Tiger Tank w/38cm RW61 Sturmmorser Kit
$54.50 $42.95
Plastic Soldier 1/72 WWII Allied M4A1 76mm Wet Stowage Sherman Tank (3) Kit
$35.99 $28.79
Home
»
Internet Hobbies Online Privacy Agreement
Internet Hobbies Online Privacy Agreement
Internet Hobbies, LLC (Internet Hobbies) is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected from those individuals that visit our website and make use of the facilities and services accurate, confidential, secure and private. Our policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with Internet Hobbies, LLC of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing policy standards.
This Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply to Internet Hobbies, LLC and thus it shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof.  Through the use of our website, you are herein consenting to the following data procedures expressed within this agreement.
COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use or frequent as means to better understand the way in which other websites garner, make use of and share information collected.
USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED
Internet Hobbies, LLC may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and or services that may be available to you from Internet Hobbies.  Internet Hobbies, LLC may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.
Internet Hobbies, LLC may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do in accordance with applicable laws and or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or required in an effort:
Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and or statutes on or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon Internet Hobbies, LLC and our website.
Maintain, safeguard and or preserve all the rights or property of Internet Hobbies, LLC: and
Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of internethobbies.com and or the general public
UNSUBSCRIBE OR OPT OUT
All users and visitors to our website have the option to discontinue receiving communications from us and or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to our website please send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to internethobbies@aol.com. Most communications and emails are delivered to you via Constant Contact, our third-party email provider. There is an unsubscribe link located at the bottom of every email.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
Our website does contain links to affiliate and other websites.  Internet Hobbies, LLC does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites.  Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.  The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our website.
SECURITY
Internet Hobbies, LLC Shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification od the user's personal information under our control.
CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY AGREEMENT
Internet Hobbies, LLC reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those changes to our website homepage so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information.  If at any point in time Internet Hobbies, LLC decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email.  Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate manner.
ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS
Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated in the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our term and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our site. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes
HOW TO CONTACT US
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website, please feel free to contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.
Email: internethobbies@aol.com
Telephone Number: 570-483-6918
Mailing Address:
Internet Hobbies, LLC504 Route 6Mayfield, PA 18433
Hot items!
